{
    "user_name": "Eleni",
    "session_complete_time": "2018-12-01 12:03:20.255439",
    "session_pk": 4,
    "session_size": 6,
    "block_size": 6,
    "policy_id": 2,
    "block_data": [
        {
            "block_id": 4,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 21,
                    "question_pk": 1006,
                    "question": "By 10.30am, we were admiring the view from a high platform, waiting to cross the deep gorge by zip line  a distance of 2,100ft.",
                    "chunk": "by zip line  ",
                    "chunk_translation": "per Zip-Leitung",
                    "answer": "by zip line",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 22,
                    "question_pk": 600,
                    "question": "I didn't talk to any teachers or family about this.",
                    "chunk": "to any teachers or family about this",
                    "chunk_translation": "zu irgendwelchen Lehrern oder Familienangeh\u00f6rigen",
                    "answer": "to any teachers or family about this",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 23,
                    "question_pk": 1052,
                    "question": "He went down the mountain, ripping through the bushes, following the sound of my voice.",
                    "chunk": "following the sound of my voice",
                    "chunk_translation": "dem Klang meiner Stimme folgend",
                    "answer": "following the sound of my voice",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 24,
                    "question_pk": 764,
                    "question": "When the lamb was breathing and more robust, I tried to stand it up, but because it had been in the birthing position for so long, its legs kept curling under.",
                    "chunk": "the lamb was breathing and more robust",
                    "chunk_translation": "Das Lamm atmete und war robuster",
                    "answer": "the lamb was breathing and was more robust",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 25,
                    "question_pk": 1138,
                    "question": "The pump continuously infuses insulin into my body, and the CGM sensor can report my blood sugar every five minutes.",
                    "chunk": "my blood sugar ",
                    "chunk_translation": "mein Blutzucker",
                    "answer": "my blood sugar",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 26,
                    "question_pk": 1230,
                    "question": "Having created something that changed and improved my own life, and having benefited from others' open-source work, I wanted to share our work so other people could use it.",
                    "chunk": "improved my own life",
                    "chunk_translation": "hat mein eigenes Leben verbessert",
                    "answer": "improved my own life",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 5,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 27,
                    "question_pk": 369,
                    "question": "When they pulled me out, they couldn't find a pulse and I wasn't breathing, so Gordon started giving me CPR.",
                    "chunk": "they pulled me out",
                    "chunk_translation": "Sie haben mich rausgezogen",
                    "answer": "they pulled me out",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 28,
                    "question_pk": 694,
                    "question": "We were climbing a steep hill when I saw a sheep lying on its side and not moving.",
                    "chunk": "on its side ",
                    "chunk_translation": "auf seiner Seite",
                    "answer": "on its side",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 29,
                    "question_pk": 317,
                    "question": "My phone was going off, but my arms were trapped so I couldn't answer.",
                    "chunk": "so I couldn't answer",
                    "chunk_translation": "also konnte ich nicht antworten",
                    "answer": "so I couldn't answer",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 30,
                    "question_pk": 252,
                    "question": "I now volunteer in schools and hospitals, dancing and talking about my leg; I do motivational speaking and teach dance classes as well as playing in my band.",
                    "chunk": "playing in my band",
                    "chunk_translation": "in meiner Band spielen",
                    "answer": "play in my band",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 31,
                    "question_pk": 2,
                    "question": "I can proudly say that last year I broke the record for the oldest person in the world to ride a rollercoaster.",
                    "chunk": "for the oldest person in the world ",
                    "chunk_translation": "f\u00fcr die \u00e4lteste Person in der Welt",
                    "answer": "for the oldest person in the world",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 32,
                    "question_pk": 778,
                    "question": "However, I finally left it on the ground without the coat  but the ewe still ignored it.",
                    "chunk": "the coat  ",
                    "chunk_translation": "der Mantel",
                    "answer": "the coat",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 6,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 33,
                    "question_pk": 368,
                    "question": "When they pulled me out, they couldn't find a pulse and I wasn't breathing, so Gordon started giving me CPR.",
                    "chunk": "When they pulled me out",
                    "chunk_translation": "Als sie mich rausgezogen haben",
                    "answer": "When they pulled me out",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 34,
                    "question_pk": 635,
                    "question": "Most of the work was in the field and I relied on my team for any written work.",
                    "chunk": "for any written work",
                    "chunk_translation": "f\u00fcr jede schriftliche Arbeit",
                    "answer": "for any written work",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 35,
                    "question_pk": 1118,
                    "question": "It's not going to happen to everybody.",
                    "chunk": "'s not going to happen to everybody",
                    "chunk_translation": "wird nicht jedem passieren",
                    "answer": "'s not going to happen to everybody",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 36,
                    "question_pk": 760,
                    "question": "Becky had read that hypothermia is a common cause of death in newborn lambs, so I wrapped it in my jacket.",
                    "chunk": "wrapped it in my jacket",
                    "chunk_translation": "wickelte es in meine Jacke",
                    "answer": "wrapped it in my jacket",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 37,
                    "question_pk": 765,
                    "question": "When the lamb was breathing and more robust, I tried to stand it up, but because it had been in the birthing position for so long, its legs kept curling under.",
                    "chunk": ", I tried to stand it up, ",
                    "chunk_translation": "Ich habe versucht, es aufzuhalten,",
                    "answer": "I tried standing it up to",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 38,
                    "question_pk": 382,
                    "question": "It was a sunny day, so I wasn't wearing very much, which is one of the reasons I didn't end up with brain damage  the hypothermia slowed my metabolism and reduced my brain's need for oxygen.",
                    "chunk": "was a sunny day",
                    "chunk_translation": "war ein sonniger Tag",
                    "answer": "was a sunny day",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 7,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 39,
                    "question_pk": 378,
                    "question": "My face was white, my lips were blue, and I had severe hypothermia, but didn't feel cold.",
                    "chunk": "My face was white",
                    "chunk_translation": "Mein Gesicht war wei\u00df",
                    "answer": "My face was white",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 40,
                    "question_pk": 1104,
                    "question": "We didn't sign any waiver at the ecopark, but we weren't entitled to compensation.",
                    "chunk": "weren't entitled to compensation",
                    "chunk_translation": "hatten keinen Anspruch auf Entsch\u00e4digung",
                    "answer": "weren't entitled to compensation",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 41,
                    "question_pk": 377,
                    "question": "My face was white, my lips were blue, and I had severe hypothermia, but didn't feel cold.",
                    "chunk": "my lips were blue",
                    "chunk_translation": "Meine Lippen waren blau",
                    "answer": "my lips were blue",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 42,
                    "question_pk": 815,
                    "question": "I was thinking, It's just going to be a cupboard that looks like a safe.",
                    "chunk": "looks like a safe",
                    "chunk_translation": "sieht wie ein Safe aus",
                    "answer": "looks like a safe",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 43,
                    "question_pk": 985,
                    "question": "Hopefully the boy will be more careful next time he plays hide and seek  but at least we know the combination to the safe now.",
                    "chunk": "will be more careful next time ",
                    "chunk_translation": "werde n\u00e4chstes mal vorsichtiger sein",
                    "answer": "will be more careful next time",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 44,
                    "question_pk": 1205,
                    "question": "I decided I was never going to leave home without it.",
                    "chunk": "was never going to leave home without it",
                    "chunk_translation": "w\u00fcrde nie ohne es verlassen",
                    "answer": "was never going to leave home without it",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 8,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 45,
                    "question_pk": 497,
                    "question": "About 10 minutes after the birth, while I was still in the medical centre and we were waiting for the ambulance, my husband scrubbed down the taxi.",
                    "chunk": "About 10 minutes after the birth",
                    "chunk_translation": "Etwa 10 Minuten nach der Geburt",
                    "answer": "About 10 minutes after the birth",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 46,
                    "question_pk": 1081,
                    "question": "At the clinic, they took x-rays and brought in a surgeon.",
                    "chunk": "brought in a surgeon",
                    "chunk_translation": "in einen Chirurgen gebracht",
                    "answer": "brought in a surgeon",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 47,
                    "question_pk": 379,
                    "question": "My face was white, my lips were blue, and I had severe hypothermia, but didn't feel cold.",
                    "chunk": ", my lips were blue, ",
                    "chunk_translation": "Meine Lippen waren blau",
                    "answer": "my lips were blue",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 48,
                    "question_pk": 747,
                    "question": "The mood was solemn, because we thought the lamb had died  but we could at least save the mother.",
                    "chunk": "we thought the lamb had died  ",
                    "chunk_translation": "wir dachten, das Lamm w\u00e4re gestorben",
                    "answer": "we thought the lamb had died",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 49,
                    "question_pk": 805,
                    "question": "I was the watch manager at a local station of the Berlin fire department that Friday, 15 December 2017.",
                    "chunk": "of the Berlin fire department ",
                    "chunk_translation": "von der Berliner Feuerwehr",
                    "answer": "of the Berlin fire department",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 50,
                    "question_pk": 721,
                    "question": "The boys were really uncertain  they felt nature should take its course  and Becky went very quiet.",
                    "chunk": "take its course  ",
                    "chunk_translation": "nimm seinen Lauf",
                    "answer": "take its course",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 9,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 51,
                    "question_pk": 590,
                    "question": "When I started secondary school, a teacher made me stand on a chair and read.",
                    "chunk": "I started secondary school",
                    "chunk_translation": "Ich habe die Sekundarschule begonnen",
                    "answer": "I started secondary school",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 52,
                    "question_pk": 1103,
                    "question": "We didn't sign any waiver at the ecopark, but we weren't entitled to compensation.",
                    "chunk": "we weren't entitled to compensation",
                    "chunk_translation": "wir hatten keinen Anspruch auf Entsch\u00e4digung",
                    "answer": "we weren't entitled to compensation",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 53,
                    "question_pk": 367,
                    "question": "When they pulled me out, they couldn't find a pulse and I wasn't breathing, so Gordon started giving me CPR.",
                    "chunk": "couldn't find a pulse ",
                    "chunk_translation": "konnte keinen Puls finden",
                    "answer": "couldn't find a pulse",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 54,
                    "question_pk": 595,
                    "question": "It was so humiliating that I would shake, and I developed a bad stutter.",
                    "chunk": "that I would shake",
                    "chunk_translation": "das w\u00fcrde ich sch\u00fctteln",
                    "answer": "that I would shake",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 55,
                    "question_pk": 759,
                    "question": "Becky had read that hypothermia is a common cause of death in newborn lambs, so I wrapped it in my jacket.",
                    "chunk": "a common cause ",
                    "chunk_translation": "eine gemeinsame Ursache",
                    "answer": "a common cause",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 56,
                    "question_pk": 48,
                    "question": "I have it on the wall in my living room, with another one that I got a year earlier for being the oldest person in the world to get their first tattoo.",
                    "chunk": "to get their first tattoo",
                    "chunk_translation": "um ihr erstes Tattoo zu bekommen",
                    "answer": "to get their first tattoo",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}